which hit a grocery store reportedly, as far as we know at this moment, killed at least 49 people.
So we have to stop and think about this. Let's stop and think about what we're seeing. 49
innocent people who were killed by a Russian airstrike while they were shopping for food
at a supermarket. That's what they were doing. And so can you imagine just walking to the grocery
store with your kids, trying to figure out what is it that you're going to make for dinner,
and you see an explosion happen where bodies are everywhere. And it's horrifying. It is
incredibly horrifying for the people of Ukraine, for the folks who are like yourselves, your
colleagues who are reporting this on the ground. And it is for these families and these kids.
So she got the perfect hairstyle for that job because ain't no way she's sleeping at night.
Just like in Friday.